Liao Jhih He

Information Technology Teacher

Address Taipei, TPE

Phone 098 613 5798

E-mail m0331005@gm.ncue.edu.tw

WWW https://sites.google.com/view/riverside-

intro/

Teaching IT 2+ years and Training student won 8th of national school skill competition computer repair job. Also designed many Embedded system projects from Hardware to Software by myself. Sometimes, it needs Full-stack web interface. As always, i'm staying in creating, leaning and sharing knowledge.

Work History

2018-07 - Current

High School IT Teacher

Shih Yu High School, New Taipei

- Developed students' computer and technology skills through demonstrations and practice.
- Enhanced student skill of robotic technology by teaching STEM robot group.
- Supported student teachers by mentoring on classroom management, lesson planning and activity organization.
- Directed after-school tutoring and mentoring program serving 8+ senior school students.

2013-07 - 2013-08

Assembly Line Worker

MAS-automation, Hsinchu

• Built 100 inches LCD product line robots, Wafer processing line robots.

Skills

Develop and Evaluate Electronics

Excellent

Design Embedded Systems and IoTs

Excellent

Full Stack Applications

Very Good

Signal Analysis and Algorithm

Very Good

Develop CNC Milling Machine G-code

Good

Education

2014-09 - 2020-06

Master of Science: Industrial Education And Technology

National Changhua University Of Education - Changhua City, Taiwan

- Thesis: Design of Wearable Pulse Wave Measuring Device.
- Majored in bio-signal measuring and analysis.

Certifications

Computer Maintenance Class B

Web Design Class C

Industrial Electronic Class C

Teach licenses

